好的，所以明天我们要做与朗诵有关的作业三，我
all right so tomorrow we're gonna have a recitation related homework three and I
recitation related homework three and I suppose we'll achieve our homework two
假设我们要在今天到期的时候完成两个作业
suppose we'll achieve our homework two already when it was due today one last
already when it was due today one last time okay all right let's post it all
好的，好的，让我们发布吧，因为我提供了扩展名，
time okay all right let's post it all right because I offer an extension and
right because I offer an extension and all would be no more extension so that
一切都不再扩展了，所以现在当我看到他们的Bailey车站时
all would be no more extension so that now when I saw their Bailey station
now when I saw their Bailey station regarding homework three and one of the
关于作业三，其中一项我们还没有讨论
regarding homework three and one of the things we haven't discussed this about
things we haven't discussed this about projects for the class okay because you
上课的项目还可以，因为您停止工作了，所以您不会去上学
projects for the class okay because you stopped working so you don't go the last
stopped working so you don't go the last week and you say to me my project is
一周，你对我说，我的项目实际上是在
week and you say to me my project is literally three days before the
literally three days before the presentations okay
演示文稿还可以，因为那样的话我真的会发疯而不是
presentations okay because then I'd really get mad and not
because then I'd really get mad and not think if in some sense you don't feel
想想如果从某种意义上讲您不觉得需要更广泛，那很好
think if in some sense you don't feel the need to have a broader it's good
the need to have a broader it's good thing to know so I can give more
要知道的事情，所以我可以给予更多的家庭作业权利，这意味着一个或一个
thing to know so I can give more homework right that means one or the
homework right that means one or the other so projects are good for you
其他项目对您也有好处，因为它使您有机会
other so projects are good for you because it gives you an opportunity to
because it gives you an opportunity to integrate things with your research and
将事物与您的研究相结合并学习新事物，我想简单
integrate things with your research and learn something new and I want simple
learn something new and I want simple projects for that way you know in other
这样的项目，您会从其他方面知道，如果您从
projects for that way you know in other ways if you take a paper from the
ways if you take a paper from the literature in this area and you
该领域的文献，您可以实现它所说的应用程序
literature in this area and you implement what it says the application
implement what it says the application examples of fantastic that's a project
梦幻般的例子，这是一个我们没有讨论过的项目，因此
examples of fantastic that's a project something we haven't discussed about so
something we haven't discussed about so that way when you give a presentation to
这样，当您向全班同学做演讲时，全班同学会学到一些新东西
that way when you give a presentation to the class the class learn something new
the class the class learn something new and we have the whole idea so it's not a
而且我们有整个想法，所以这不是什么都不做然后假装的方法
and we have the whole idea so it's not a way to do nothing and then pretend
way to do nothing and then pretend here's my project okay that's not very
这是我的项目，对您自己和我来说都不是一件好事
here's my project okay that's not very good for yourself for me and for the
good for yourself for me and for the university all right
大学还好，我还是建议我们瘦如
university all right still may I suggest that we thin like to
still may I suggest that we thin like to the next week we'll talk you come up
下周我们会说您为您的项目准备了一个applet，好吧，
the next week we'll talk you come up with an applet for your project okay and
with an applet for your project okay and this time you won't be able to change it
这次您将无法更改它，因此请使用
this time you won't be able to change it so make your abstract artwork with at
so make your abstract artwork with at least one reference so I know that
至少有一个参考资料，所以我知道您受某些事情的束缚，好吗？
least one reference so I know that you're bounded by something okay you
you're bounded by something okay you miss the most important or the clause
错过最重要的条款
而且您知道上一堂课还有几张幻灯片，但是
you're bounded by something okay you miss the most important or the clause
and you know there were a few more slides left on the last lecture but is
而且您知道上一堂课还有几张幻灯片，但是
slides left on the last lecture but is now posted because I realized we forgot
现在发布，因为我意识到我们忘记了以忘记的方式发布
now posted because I realized we forgot to post it the same way we forgot to
to post it the same way we forgot to post the videos all right take note so
将视频发布好吧，请注意，所以我们需要阅读此发布的内容，所以今天我是
post the videos all right take note so we need to read this posted so today I'm
we need to read this posted so today I'm going to do is I'm going to move past
我要做的是超越求和积算法并进行讨论
going to do is I'm going to move past the sum-product algorithm and discussed
the sum-product algorithm and discussed first the Maxum algorithm and we
首先是Maxum算法，我们在某种程度上讨论了这是什么
first the Maxum algorithm and we discussed what that is in sort of very
discussed what that is in sort of very general terms then we'll actually take a
一般而言，如果没有其他条件，我们实际上会向后退一步
general terms then we'll actually take a step backwards if nothing else for
step backwards if nothing else for historical reasons and give you a few
历史原因，并为您提供一些幻灯片示例的幻灯片
historical reasons and give you a few slides on something that the sample of a
slides on something that the sample of a subtype of the sum-product I will be
我将对总积的子类型进行拍照
subtype of the sum-product I will be photographed
photographed that is called belief propagation and at
这就是所谓的信念传播，至少您需要知道何时看到
that is called belief propagation and at least you need to know when you see a
least you need to know when you see a need because people talk about belief
需要，因为人们谈论信仰传播，这基本上是
need because people talk about belief propagation it's basically a subset of
propagation it's basically a subset of what we already have done but I want to
我们已经完成的工作，但我只想覆盖几张幻灯片，以便您看到
what we already have done but I want to just cover it a few slides so you see
just cover it a few slides so you see the notation coming from people that are
来自以信息科学为基础的人们的表示法是一种
the notation coming from people that are grounded in information science is sort
grounded in information science is sort of a different perspective of what we
到现在为止我们所做的事情有不同的看法
of a different perspective of what we have done up to now
have done up to now and assuming we have Pauline I'm gonna
并假设我们有Pauline，我将开始讨论另一个确切的推论
and assuming we have Pauline I'm gonna start to discuss another exact inference
start to discuss another exact inference algorithm for general graphs which is
通用图的算法，称为结点树算法
algorithm for general graphs which is called the junction tree algorithm I am
called the junction tree algorithm I am NOT going to give you all the details
不会为您提供所有详细信息的一些简单示例，然后
NOT going to give you all the details some sort of simple examples and then
some sort of simple examples and then when we come back on Tuesday I will
当我们星期二回来时，我将提供
when we come back on Tuesday I will provide some of the details from the
provide some of the details from the different versions of this algorithms
该算法的不同版本，希望您可以执行以下任一操作
different versions of this algorithms and hopefully you can do one of these
and hopefully you can do one of these implementations in your homework once we
一旦我们涵盖了这些内容，或者接下来的内容，您的家庭作业中的实施
implementations in your homework once we cover these things or maybe the next
cover these things or maybe the next several lectures we're going to go
我们将向后讲几讲，并举例说明
several lectures we're going to go backwards and do examples for example
backwards and do examples for example for hidden Markov models for state-space
用于状态空间模型的隐马尔可夫模型，因此我们将尝试重新审视
for hidden Markov models for state-space models so we are going to try to revisit
models so we are going to try to revisit this knowledge in specific contexts so
在特定上下文中的这种知识，因此在某种意义上，您还有另一种标记
this knowledge in specific contexts so in some sense you have another mark for
in some sense you have another mark for short the good luck to these notes and
祝您好运，并再次阅读
short the good luck to these notes and read them again
read them again okay because we will release them on
好的，因为我们将在特定示例中发布它们，所以让我介绍一下
okay because we will release them on specific examples so let me introduce
specific examples so let me introduce this magical algorithm when what the
这个神奇的算法，当问题出在什么地方时
this magical algorithm when what the problem is about so obviously in
problem is about so obviously in probabilistic graphical models we can
概率图形模型我们可以对联合概率分布建模
probabilistic graphical models we can model the joint probability distribution
model the joint probability distribution of many of the variables and we figure
许多变量中，我们找出了如何根据给定的证据进行计算
of many of the variables and we figure out how given some evidence we compute
out how given some evidence we compute conditionals to marginal stuffing size
边际填充大小的条件，所以现在让我们说我们有一个
conditionals to marginal stuffing size up so right now let's say we have a
up so right now let's say we have a graph to represent a probability P of X
图来表示X的概率P，我们想找到该值
graph to represent a probability P of X and we want to find the value the
and we want to find the value the maximum effects that maximizes this P of
使X的P以及X的P的最大值最大化的最大效果
maximum effects that maximizes this P of X and also that maximum value of P of X
X and also that maximum value of P of X so if you think that P of X being the
因此，如果您认为X的繁荣就是Oracle的兴旺，可能是在问什么
so if you think that P of X being the prosperity Oracle may be asking what's
prosperity Oracle may be asking what's the value of x of Knox why is the
Knox的x值为什么是后验值，而不是最大值
the value of x of Knox why is the posterior and what is not maximum value
posterior and what is not maximum value okay so the difficulty with this problem
好吧，所以这个问题的难处在于，如果您最大化边际
okay so the difficulty with this problem right is that if you maximize marginals
right is that if you maximize marginals what you will get if you put all the XS
如果将所有XS放在一起，将得到的结果与我们必须位于的轴不同
what you will get if you put all the XS together is not the same axis as we must
together is not the same axis as we must mies the
限制联合分配并进行
mies the the Joint Distribution and carry sort of
the Joint Distribution and carry sort of a trivial example we have binary
一个简单的例子，我们有二元粒子部分Y列表是
a trivial example we have binary particle section Y lists are the
particle section Y lists are the corresponding probabilities for these
这些物品的相应概率可以使您获得价值石
corresponding probabilities for these items to take the value stone you can
items to take the value stone you can see the value of the probability of X
看到X的概率值等于0.6 X的概率值等于
see the value of the probability of X equal to 0.6 the probability of X equal
equal to 0.6 the probability of X equal ones points y equal to 0.7 and why port
y等于0.7，为什么端口1是43，所以X会影响参数
ones points y equal to 0.7 and why port 1 is 43 so X the argument affects that
1 is 43 so X the argument affects that takes gives you the maximum probability
可以给您边际的最大概率为X等于0右
takes gives you the maximum probability for the marginal is X equal to 0 right
for the marginal is X equal to 0 right we're doing and the maximum the kind of
我们正在做的是，Y的种类最大，所以Y的边沿是y
we're doing and the maximum the kind of Y that much mice the marginal of Y is y
Y that much mice the marginal of Y is y equal to 0 but if you look at this table
等于0，但如果您查看此表，这基本上是联合
equal to 0 but if you look at this table the this is basically the joint
the this is basically the joint probability distribution affection y the
概率分布影响y当x等于1和y时发生最大值
probability distribution affection y the maximum happens when x equals 1 and y
maximum happens when x equals 1 and y equal to 0 not the same bar right so I
等于0，不是相同的小节，所以我的意思是这是一个示例，但您可以
equal to 0 not the same bar right so I mean this is one example but you can
mean this is one example but you can generalize this and you can see that you
一概而论，您会看到，您知道自己必须非常幸运，
generalize this and you can see that you know you have to be very lucky where the
know you have to be very lucky where the axis of maximize the margin of the chain
最大化链的边缘的轴为关节的最大化轴，因此
axis of maximize the margin of the chain as the axis of maximize the the joint so
as the axis of maximize the the joint so what we need to do is we need to find an
我们需要做的是找到一种算法，可以使用
what we need to do is we need to find an algorithm that we can do this with the
algorithm that we can do this with the same efficiency of doing influencing
产生影响图的效率相同，或者您可以使用算法
same efficiency of doing influencing graphs or you can have algorithm and in
graphs or you can have algorithm and in principle looks identical to doing
原理看起来与在图形中进行推断完全相同-有些
principle looks identical to doing inference in graphs all right - some
inference in graphs all right - some small perturbations
小扰动
你知道我提到过很多12s算法，实际上它们是
inference in graphs all right - some small perturbations
you know I have mentioned that the lots of 12s algorithms really they they're
你知道我提到过很多12s算法，实际上它们是
of 12s algorithms really they they're very common in you know in dynamic
您在动态编程源中了解所有事物的情况非常普遍
very common in you know in dynamic programming source of all things you
programming source of all things you today they will also look like dynamic
今天，它们看起来也像动态编程，所以我们可以说整个
today they will also look like dynamic programming so let's say this whole of
programming so let's say this whole of this tower evidence node this is a bunch
这个塔证据节点这是一堆我们并不在乎的节点
this tower evidence node this is a bunch of nodes we don't really care and this
of nodes we don't really care and this list the query nodes all right so we're
正确列出查询节点，以便我们感兴趣时进行计算
list the query nodes all right so we're interested to compute when we did
interested to compute when we did increase to compute the probability of X
增加以计算给定XT的X F概率以及
increase to compute the probability of X F given XT and the whole idea of the
F given XT and the whole idea of the sum-product algorithm is to do sort of
sum-product算法是一种有效的方法，可以对
sum-product algorithm is to do sort of estimations in an efficient way on the
estimations in an efficient way on the glass so now we want to find react but
玻璃，所以现在我们想找到反应，但是将这个概率最大化，除了
glass so now we want to find react but maximize is this the probability except
maximize is this the probability except given the evidence which is basically
给定的证据与最大化概率基本相同
given the evidence which is basically the same as the probability maximizing
the same as the probability maximizing the joint because you know if you write
关节，因为您知道您是否写的是关节除以证据
the joint because you know if you write is the joint divided by the evidence the
is the joint divided by the evidence the evidence doesn't accept so this is the
证据不接受，所以这是一样的，如此有效地将这种光保持在
evidence doesn't accept so this is the same so effectively this light stays in
same so effectively this light stays in evidence or not doesn't matter you can
证据与否无关紧要，您可以解决寻找额外人员的问题
evidence or not doesn't matter you can treat the problem of finding the extras
treat the problem of finding the extras maximizes the joint all this probability
最大化联合所有这些证据的可能性基本上是
maximizes the joint all this probability for evidence account is basically the
for evidence account is basically the same way all right so in this case I
同样的方法，所以在这种情况下，我的意思是你可以把极端
same way all right so in this case I mean you can put the extreme to the
mean you can put the extreme to the given value stand still you have the
给定值不动，您拥有联合分布，并用
given value stand still you have the joint distribution and maximize it with
joint distribution and maximize it with respect to itself right
现在尊重自己，我们将能够信奉的宗教
respect to itself right now the religion that we will be able to
now the religion that we will be able to expand the inference algorithms to do
扩展推理算法来做到这一点，标记算法具有
expand the inference algorithms to do this marks algorithm has the part of the
this marks algorithm has the part of the operator marks distribute over
运算符标记通过乘积的分布方式与我们向您展示的方式相同
operator marks distribute over multiplication the same way we show you
multiplication the same way we show you know with the summation when we did
当我们进行推理算法时，总和就知道了，例如
know with the summation when we did inference algorithms so for example this
inference algorithms so for example this is what we took advantage to push
是我们利用优势在我们知道的世界中进行求和的方法
is what we took advantage to push summations in worlds you know when we
summations in worlds you know when we did elimination algorithms and you can
做了消除算法，当我们
did elimination algorithms and you can see the same thing is applicable when we
see the same thing is applicable when we have maximization so the maximum a V and
具有最大值，因此最大值V和H 3等于最大值的乘积
have maximization so the maximum a V and H 3 is the same as a times the maximum
H 3 is the same as a times the maximum BC and and this distribution of the
BC和此匹配运算符的分布将相乘
BC and and this distribution of the match operator of a multiplication will
match operator of a multiplication will allow us to discipline the same sort of
允许我们训练与淘汰时相同的想法
allow us to discipline the same sort of idea that we did with elimination when
idea that we did with elimination when we were pushing salacious treatments so
我们一直在进行卑鄙的治疗，所以我们可以满足我们代数
we were pushing salacious treatments so we can be met let's algebra I'm doing
we can be met let's algebra I'm doing all of them simultaneously so if you
所有这些都同时发生，所以如果您说停止意识到
all of them simultaneously so if you have let's say stopped realization that
have let's say stopped realization that involves X 1 X 2 X 3 functions of the
涉及三个的X 1 X 2 X 3函数，并且您要查找X 1 X 2 X
involves X 1 X 2 X 3 functions of the three and you want to find the X 1 X 2 X
three and you want to find the X 1 X 2 X 3 that maximize this product obviously
3可以最大程度地利用此产品，您显然可以开始推动很多
3 that maximize this product obviously you can start pushing some of the much
you can start pushing some of the much of the latest in works I mean in this
我的意思是在这种情况下当然是微不足道的，因为8 I
of the latest in works I mean in this case of course it is trivial because 8 I
case of course it is trivial because 8 I do not put any x1 or x2 here then it
不要在这里放置任何x1或x2，然后在这里放置其他任何东西，但显然
do not put any x1 or x2 here then it with anything else here so but obviously
with anything else here so but obviously you've got the spirit that somehow we
您的精神使我们能够以某种方式推动此门户网站正常运行，因此
you've got the spirit that somehow we will be able to push this portal ok so
will be able to push this portal ok so here is the simple chain problem that we
这是我们到处都看到的无向图的简单链条问题
here is the simple chain problem that we have seen everywhere undirected graph
have seen everywhere undirected graph let's say we define this these are the
假设我们定义这些为最大集团，因此我们用
let's say we define this these are the maximal cliques so we define this with a
maximal cliques so we define this with a potential so I want to try to 3 psi n
电位，所以我想尝试3 psi n减去1 n，所以如果您想找到X的
potential so I want to try to 3 psi n minus 1 n so if you want find the X of
minus 1 n so if you want find the X of maximizes first so effectively what you
首先最大化最大化，那么您需要做的就是达到最大化
maximizes first so effectively what you need to do is arrive this maximization
need to do is arrive this maximization of
以您在赛车上看到的方式
of Racing on the way that you see on the
Racing on the way that you see on the bottom okay this is gonna be sort of the
底部好吧，这有点有点复杂，但是我们需要能够
bottom okay this is gonna be sort of the little complexity but we need to be able
little complexity but we need to be able to account for so here we are going x10
考虑到这一点，我们在这里将x10出现在您的列表标签上，这样您就可以
to account for so here we are going x10 appears on your list tab so you can
appears on your list tab so you can actually do this maximization then you
实际进行这种最大化，然后您将得到一些仅取决于
actually do this maximization then you will get something that depends only on
will get something that depends only on n minus 1 so this combined with the
n减去1，再加上先前的电位，您可以
n minus 1 so this combined with the previous potential you can do the
previous potential you can do the maximization or n minus 1 etc etc until
最大化或n减1等，直到基本上可以在这里进行最大化
maximization or n minus 1 etc etc until basically you can do a maximization here
basically you can do a maximization here with respect to x1 actually if you
关于x1实际上，如果您了解此示例，
with respect to x1 actually if you understand this this example you
understand this this example you understand everything in the picture for
了解此最大算法和此图中的所有内容
understand everything in the picture for this maximum algorithm and this
this maximum algorithm and this elimination algorithm and actually I
消除算法，实际上我从较早的版本之一复制了剧情
elimination algorithm and actually I copied the plot from one of our earlier
copied the plot from one of our earlier lectures where we were eliminating first
讲座中，我们消除了第一个X 6和X 5 X 4 X 3 X 2和X 1，所以在
lectures where we were eliminating first X 6 and X 5 X 4 X 3 X 2 and X 1 so in
X 6 and X 5 X 4 X 3 X 2 and X 1 so in this case we want to find the maximum
在这种情况下，我们想要找到X 1到6的联合概率的最大值
this case we want to find the maximum that the joint probability of X 1 to 6
that the joint probability of X 1 to 6 but I take here vertex tricks is evident
但我认为这里的顶点技巧很明显，正如我们之前所说的那样，
but I take here vertex tricks is evident and as we said before it doesn't really
and as we said before it doesn't really make any difference
没关系，所以这是确切的授权
make any difference ok so this is the exact authorization
ok so this is the exact authorization nothing special again be FX 1 X 2 given
没什么特别的是FX 1 X 2给定X 1 X 3 X 1 X 5 X 3 X 6给定X 2和X
nothing special again be FX 1 X 2 given X 1 X 3 X 1 X 5 X 3 X 6 given X 2 and X
X 1 X 3 X 1 X 5 X 3 X 6 given X 2 and X 5 X 4 given X X 4 given X 2 X 4 X 4
5 X 4给定XX 4给定X 2 X 4 X 4给定键
5 X 4 given X X 4 given X 2 X 4 X 4 given a key to okay
given a key to okay and then I put Delta and evidence
然后我将Delta和证据潜力固定在x 6的值上
and then I put Delta and evidence potential there to fix the value of x 6
potential there to fix the value of x 6 of X 6 bar
X 6巴
所以我们要压缩最大化相同的单词
potential there to fix the value of x 6 of X 6 bar
so we is compressing the maximization same words
所以我们要压缩最大化相同的单词
same words so we suppress what parents involve sex
所以我们压制父母涉及性棒的事情，这是列表时间
so we suppress what parents involve sex sticks and there is list times this
sticks and there is list times this potential but the only things that
潜力，但唯一涉及六个六的事物，因此我们实际上可以找到
potential but the only things that involve six six so we can actually find
involve six six so we can actually find the max2 of this with respect to its
相对于第六个的max2，当我们说要找到一个
the max2 of this with respect to its sixth when we say we're going to find an
sixth when we say we're going to find an option of this with respect to the sixth
对于第六个访问者，可以选择x 2 x 5的可能值
option of this with respect to the sixth vistors for possible values of x 2 x 5
vistors for possible values of x 2 x 5 because in office in a function x 10 x 5
因为在办公室中，函数x 10 x 5个参数给定了，所以我
because in office in a function x 10 x 5 arguments then that given right so i
arguments then that given right so i mean this time a function of the three
意思是这次这是三个参数的函数
mean this time a function of the three arguments okay
arguments okay so X 3 X 5 arbitrary here so when we
X 3 X 5在这里是任意的，所以当我们必须相对于X 6合并时，我们有
so X 3 X 5 arbitrary here so when we must merge with respect to X 6 we have
must merge with respect to X 6 we have to do for the possible values of X 3 X 5
为X 3 X 5的可能值做这是非常重要的一步，好吧，
to do for the possible values of X 3 X 5 this is very important move on okay you
this is very important move on okay you do this maximization and the same way we
做这个最大化，和我们消除的方法一样，我们称之为
do this maximization and the same way we did with elimination we're going to call
did with elimination we're going to call this 8 6 because 6 is the now to
这个8 6因为6是现在要消除的参数
this 8 6 because 6 is the now to eliminate and the arguments are so
eliminate and the arguments are so you're going to have to compute this
您将必须计算此预期的抖动，无论如何都将其称为
you're going to have to compute this expected shakes anyway call it the
expected shakes anyway call it the function HX X to connect start we did
功能HX X连接开始，我们用消除做了同样的事情，但是在
function HX X to connect start we did the same thing with elimination but in
the same thing with elimination but in elimination what did we go to add 6
消除我们去加了6
所以总的来说，如果我们必须在这里进行分析，我们就不要停止，我们必须
the same thing with elimination but in elimination what did we go to add 6
so to sum it all right if we must analyze it here we don't stop we must
所以总的来说，如果我们必须在这里进行分析，我们就不要停止，我们必须
analyze it here we don't stop we must okay the terms that involve x5 obviously
好吧，涉及到x5的术语显然是原始的
okay the terms that involve x5 obviously there was this term from the original
there was this term from the original distribution times this new potentially
分布乘以这个新的潜在值六倍，因此这里的三个参数
distribution times this new potentially six so again the three arguments here
six so again the three arguments here are three and few so that we will get a
是三个而只有三个，所以我们将得到一个称为H的新功能5
are three and few so that we will get a new function that is called H five
new function that is called H five because five is eliminated affects to
因为消除了五个影响将三个结合起来，那么我们需要消除
because five is eliminated affects to combine three then we need to eliminate
combine three then we need to eliminate on with much margin export this function
在大量保证金出口的情况下，让我们看看我们需要我们所说的
on with much margin export this function would be let's see we need what we said
would be let's see we need what we said to do it on Expo right so this function
在世博会上做，所以这个功能很好地发挥了所有律师的作用。
to do it on Expo right so this function well playing it all attorney this blue
well playing it all attorney this blue thing that you see here all right so
您在这里看到的东西很好，所以这将是X的函数，仅
thing that you see here all right so this would be a function of X to only
this would be a function of X to only which is H porn effective then we need
这是H色情有效的影片，那么我们需要大量选择三个
which is H porn effective then we need to much my selects three which will
to much my selects three which will involve this argument last this function
涉及此参数最后一个函数H五个这是您在这里看到的
involve this argument last this function H five this is what you see here this is
H five this is what you see here this is a three of x1 and x2 then we need to
x1和x2的三个，那么我们需要在x2上最大化具有XQ的所有内容
a three of x1 and x2 then we need to maximize on x2 everything that has X Q
maximize on x2 everything that has X Q which is this x dot time to the stage
这是到第三阶段的x点时间，我们将此函数称为a到x one
which is this x dot time to the stage three we call this function a to x one
three we call this function a to x one and then we're vision because we only
然后我们就是愿景，因为我们只有x1的函数，我们可以将其最大化
and then we're vision because we only have a function of x1 we can maximize it
have a function of x1 we can maximize it and that will give me you know will give
那会给我，你知道会给你一些价值，那就是
and that will give me you know will give you something a value and that's the
you something a value and that's the maximum of this probability okay so for
这个可能性最大，所以在很多方面
maximum of this probability okay so for many ways
与消除算法没什么大不了的
there is nothing very different from the elimination algorithm okay
这里有些东西什么也没说，所以我们
there is something this process here doesn't say anything about so we
doesn't say anything about so we computed the maximum of this probability
计算出该概率的最大值
X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4 X 5的分布，使该联合概率最大化
doesn't say anything about so we computed the maximum of this probability
distribution of X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4 X 5 that maximize that joint probability what are
X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4 X 5的分布，使该联合概率最大化
maximize that joint probability what are you going to tell you so this calculated
你要告诉你，所以这计算了关节的极点，现在我是
you going to tell you so this calculated the maxim of the joint and now I am
the maxim of the joint and now I am asking you what is what are the values
问你X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4 X 5的值是多少，但它们在一起
asking you what is what are the values of X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4 X 5 but together they
of X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4 X 5 but together they maximize this distribution so I want you
最大化这种分布，所以我希望您看看那里的大面积并尝试
maximize this distribution so I want you to look in the big areas there and try
to look in the big areas there and try to think what everything is going to be
想一想一切将是什么样，现在您将看到10张幻灯片，
to think what everything is going to be that you will see 10 slides from now and
that you will see 10 slides from now and you will look more confusing in verse 10
除非您真的
you will look more confusing in verse 10 slides down the road unless you actually
slides down the road unless you actually understand here how you're going to do
在这里了解您将如何在这里做
understand here how you're going to do it here
在这种情况下，我们让我确保从通往树叶的途中的树叶安全
in this case right we let me make it safe from the leaves on the way to the
safe from the leaves on the way to the root so let's call this thing okay can
根，让我们称这件事好吧，除了我们拥有的方式之外，您可以做任何您想做的
root so let's call this thing okay can do anything you want but the way we have
do anything you want but the way we have done it in this elimination sequence X 1
按照消除顺序X 1是根，这是最大化的根
done it in this elimination sequence X 1 is the root so that's one that maximizes
is the root so that's one that maximizes this distribution the giant do we know
这个分布巨人，我们是否知道前缀岩石这么多
this distribution the giant do we know the prefix rock that much much
the prefix rock that much much distribution notice what in the last
分配注意在最后一对中该问题权只有一个
distribution notice what in the last pair this problem right has only one
pair this problem right has only one argument here which sexual so do we know
这里的论点是什么性的，所以我们知道x1可以计算X 1是的，这是怎么回事
argument here which sexual so do we know x1 can we compute X 1 yes this how are
x1 can we compute X 1 yes this how are you going to compute X 2 in this
您将在此计算中计算X 2以允许您现在进行计算
you going to compute X 2 in this calculation to allow you to compute now
calculation to allow you to compute now the value of x do you remember when we
x的值，您还记得我们执行此操作时所计算出的x的值吗
the value of x do you remember when we computed this when we perform this
computed this when we perform this maximization so what values of x1 we did
最大化，所以我们对x1的值做了什么，对于x 1的值做了什么，我们做到了
maximization so what values of x1 we did it for what value of x 1 did we do this
it for what value of x 1 did we do this maximization with spectryx - it's in the
用spectryx最大化-在定义中您可以看到
maximization with spectryx - it's in the definition you can see
不，但这是一种文化，然后我们所做的就是揭示电子，
no but this is a culture and then what we do is revealed electron that you
we do is revealed electron that you completed here and that function will
在这里完成，该功能将为您提供最佳的x2
completed here and that function will give you the optimal x2
是的等于我这是它的最佳价值，首先尝试思考三个
yes are equal to I this is the optimum value of its to first try thinking three
value of its to first try thinking three vistas thereafter on volume
此后按体积计算的远景现在我们用电子计算出
vistas thereafter on volume now we computed with my electron is when
now we computed with my electron is when we live payload so we can go back to the
我们使用有效载荷，因此如果x1，我们可以返回到每个宫殿的功能
we live payload so we can go back to the function the palace for each one if x1
function the palace for each one if x1 what's the corresponding X to the
最大化的对应X是多少，小猪x1 + 2 x2等于
what's the corresponding X to the maximizes this and piggy x1 + 2 x2 equal
maximizes this and piggy x1 + 2 x2 equal to that so degree when we beat
达到这样的程度，当我们战胜淘汰赛时，我将写
to that so degree when we beat elimination I'm going to write from the
elimination I'm going to write from the list of every we marginalize now it's
现在我们每个被边缘化的列表都可以找到这个联合的最大值
list of every we marginalize now it's okay to find the maximum of this joint
okay to find the maximum of this joint distribution yes it's a terrible
分配是的，这是从生命到世界的可怕计算
distribution yes it's a terrible calculation from the lives to the world
calculation from the lives to the world but to find the extra store do the job
但是要找到额外的商店来做这项工作，我们必须倒退，所以我们现在
but to find the extra store do the job we have to go backwards right so we now
we have to go backwards right so we now have to go and say you know what
必须说您知道我们知道X 2将最大化
have to go and say you know what we know that the X 2's would maximize
we know that the X 2's would maximize this for each X 1 but we know X 1 so
对于每个X 1，但是我们知道X 1，所以这将为您提供适当的X 2和
this for each X 1 but we know X 1 so this will give you the proper X 2 and
this will give you the proper X 2 and then he worked here in second awhat to
然后他第二次在这里工作为了做到这一点，我需要知道X 1
then he worked here in second awhat to do this maximization I need to know X 1
do this maximization I need to know X 1 and so in between X 1 and you connect
因此，在X 1之间，您将它们连接在一起不会产生什么影响
and so in between X 1 and you connect them together what is not going to make
them together what is not going to make an optimal path for the joint is the
关节的最佳途径是美丽
an optimal path for the joint is the beauty
beauty all right so there are infinite paths
好的，所以有无限的路径，现在您需要选择最佳路径
all right so there are infinite paths now you need to select the optimal path
now you need to select the optimal path by going back to the help you receive
返回到您获得的帮助之后，我们所描述的实际上是
by going back to the help you receive that so what we describe is actually
that so what we describe is actually very general but the implementation of
非常笼统，但是这种小语言的实现确实扭曲了它
very general but the implementation of this the little language does distort it
this the little language does distort it a lot of models is called a return be
很多模型被称为收益远离那个系统从头到尾的移动
a lot of models is called a return be away from that system moves from the end
away from that system moves from the end of the most famous ability computer
最著名的计算机科学能力还可以
of the most famous ability computer science okay
science okay it's used everywhere okay so so this is
到处都可以使用，所以这是一个非常有用的问题，而您
it's used everywhere okay so so this is a very useful problem okay and and you
a very useful problem okay and and you can appreciate basically that now yes we
基本上可以体会到，现在是的，我们继续前进
can appreciate basically that now yes we go forward
go forward we go from the links to the route
我们基本上从链接到路线去找到最大值，但是
we go from the links to the route basically to find the maximum but to
basically to find the maximum but to find the x that leads to a maximum we
找到导致最大值的x，我们必须倒退，所以有一个
find the x that leads to a maximum we have to go backwards so there is a
have to go backwards so there is a forward calculation is a powerful
正向计算是一种功能强大的计算，与我们所做的类似
forward calculation is a powerful calculation similarly what we did with
calculation similarly what we did with the sample based on away with sending
该样本基于远离并基本上向前和向后发送消息
the sample based on away with sending messages forward and backward basically
messages forward and backward basically to be able to compute marginals turn and
就能计算出边际转弯，诸如操作之类的东西基本上就是你
to be able to compute marginals turn and things like operation is basically you
things like operation is basically you just discuss it right so it looks the
只是讨论正确，所以它看起来是初始化的，证据是
just discuss it right so it looks the the initialization and the evidence is
the initialization and the evidence is exactly the same algorithm that you use
与您在中使用的算法完全相同，实际上这是算法
exactly the same algorithm that you use in the in actually this is the algorithm
in the in actually this is the algorithm that we used for the elimination you
我们用于消除的过程，您知道，但是我在这里称其为
that we used for the elimination you know but here I call this I suppose is
know but here I call this I suppose is hope is not a typo
希望不是错别字好吧，我想我从
hope is not a typo all right I mean I suppose not much from
all right I mean I suppose not much from you know SQL for Staters but here I
您知道针对Staters的SQL，但在这里我可能是针对一般发行版的
you know SQL for Staters but here I maybe this for the general distribution
maybe this for the general distribution with the map so anyways we initialize
与地图，所以无论如何我们都初始化相同的东西，我们有向图
with the map so anyways we initialize the same we have a directed graph we
the same we have a directed graph we initialize all the potentials we put
初始化所有可能的东西，我们将它们放到我们介绍的活动列表中
initialize all the potentials we put them on active list we introduced
them on active list we introduced evidence potentials the way we did
以以前的方式证明潜力，现在我们必须进行更新
evidence potentials the way we did before and now we have to do the update
before and now we have to do the update all right and the updates are basically
没关系，这些更新基本上就是我所描述的
all right and the updates are basically what I described with a particular
what I described with a particular example if you pick up
例如，如果您在他们的第90个节点I处获得淘汰，则您
example if you pick up elimination over their 90th node I you
elimination over their 90th node I you find all the potentials that are
找到所有有趣的节点I的潜力，然后执行
find all the potentials that are interesting node I and then you do
interesting node I and then you do stream optimize with respect to X I all
关于XI的流优化
stream optimize with respect to X I all right
right and once you maximize with respective
一旦您在各自的时间中实现最大化，就可以称呼这种新的潜力
and once you maximize with respective time you call this new potential you
time you call this new potential you will put this in potential of the octave
这次可以将其置于八度音阶列表中
will put this in potential of the octave list okay this time the remaining
list okay this time the remaining knowledge from the elimination click and
消除点击后的知识，然后进行关键的操作，直到基本上
knowledge from the elimination click and then the key proceeding until basically
then the key proceeding until basically you whatever number you gave up when you
您在根节点最大化时放弃的任何数量
you whatever number you gave up when you maximized with respect to the root node
maximized with respect to the root node will be the max want to join
将是最大的希望共同参与分配优化的人否
will be the max want to join distribution optimization jointly no
distribution optimization jointly no it's right that you complete for
是的，您完成了不一样的事情，就知道那里没有
it's right that you complete for different you know there are there's no
different you know there are there's no you shall not eliminate it but you see
您不会消除它，但是您认为还可以，因此对于此值
you shall not eliminate it but you see okay so for the possible values of this
okay so for the possible values of this you need need to keep track what is the
您需要跟踪什么是最大化您的价值XI好的，然后
you need need to keep track what is the maximize your value X I okay and then
maximize your value X I okay and then when units eventually the root and you
当单位最终成为根并计算实际音符时，最大化
when units eventually the root and you calculate the actual note the maximizes
calculate the actual note the maximizes the final potential that you get when
当您倒退时可以得到的最终潜力可以计算
the final potential that you get when you go backwards and you can calculate
you go backwards and you can calculate the remaining of the
剩下的，所以这不仅是声音不错，而且
the remaining of the so this is not solely the sound good but
so this is not solely the sound good but basically what I described
基本上是我所描述的
因此，实际上，如果您认为这是一个计算和神秘主义，
so this is not solely the sound good but basically what I described
so actually we the the calculations and the mysticism if you think of this as a
因此，实际上，如果您认为这是一个计算和神秘主义，
the mysticism if you think of this as a message passing algorithm it looks
消息传递算法，它看起来与我们为
message passing algorithm it looks identical to what we have done for the
identical to what we have done for the you know the the only difference except
你知道唯一的区别，除了求和，我们现在有了最大化
you know the the only difference except of summations we now have maximization
of summations we now have maximization arguments all right so what the shown
参数很好，所以这里显示的基本上是完成后的内容，
arguments all right so what the shown here is basically when you are done and
here is basically when you are done and you have rates of the route all right so
您有正确的路线费率，那么这就是我们直接拥有的费率
you have rates of the route all right so then here it's the rate directly we have
then here it's the rate directly we have an evidence potential and the message is
潜在的证据，信息是从根源传来的
an evidence potential and the message is coming from the children of the root to
coming from the children of the root to the root all right and then what you
根就好了，然后您需要做的唯一论点是
the root all right and then what you need to do the only argument here is to
need to do the only argument here is to accept and they need most maximize with
接受，他们需要最大程度地接受所有权利，以便我们为您提供
accept and they need most maximize with accept all right so that we give you the
accept all right so that we give you the argument you know the know what's the
您知道的参数知道根音符的值是什么
argument you know the know what's the value of the root note that the
value of the root note that the maximization and then what we have to do
最大化，然后我们要做的就是建立融洽的关系
maximization and then what we have to do is you have to build rapport we
is you have to build rapport we distribute command that you see here -
分发您在此处看到的命令-实际上，我们必须共同加入
distribute command that you see here - actually that jointly we must join
actually that jointly we must join distribution at the message an arbitrary
在消息中分配任意的“ J”，并尝试正是我们所拥有的
distribution at the message an arbitrary no J's and try it's exactly what we have
no J's and try it's exactly what we have looked with with elimination algorithm
用消除算法查看之前，这是有潜力的证据
looked with with elimination algorithm before this is the evidence potential
before this is the evidence potential this is the parent potential phi xj and
这是父势phi xj，而这个xi消息是转到节点J的消息
this is the parent potential phi xj and this xi message is the go to node J
this xi message is the go to node J except I so basically the J sense try
除了我基本上是J感觉，尝试并不能证明这种连接潜力
except I so basically the J sense try it's not evidence this join potential
it's not evidence this join potential and all the masses are having to J
除了现在的I，所有的群众都不得不去J
and all the masses are having to J except from now the I
except from now the I the basement of standing of three
三个中立的地位的地下室说，好吧，我需要得到
the basement of standing of three neutralizing it said okay I need to get
neutralizing it said okay I need to get back the XJ right so we find the match
向右退XJ，所以我们找到要移到此处的匹配项，因此我们计算出
back the XJ right so we find the match to move here so we compute the XJ that
to move here so we compute the XJ that maximizes this alright but we need to
最大限度地提高此功能，但我们需要根据XI通知找到它
maximizes this alright but we need to find this as a function of X I notice
find this as a function of X I notice from children effects and then who is
从儿童效果开始，然后这又是谁呢，又往下走了一步
from children effects and then who is this the bound and one step further down
this the bound and one step further down and we were to compute basically both
我们基本上要计算两个出口，至少到
and we were to compute basically both the exits up to at least the point is
the exits up to at least the point is right if you calculate the X J's don't
对，如果您计算出X J不会使整个运动量最大化
right if you calculate the X J's don't maximize this whole bunch of exercise
maximize this whole bunch of exercise all right and unique need to keep track
正确和独特的需求，使我的电池地图一无所获，因为
all right and unique need to keep track nothing about maps my batteries because
nothing about maps my batteries because you will need to do this message passing
您将需要为此算法传递大量的消息，而且
you will need to do this message passing on this much for that algorithm but also
on this much for that algorithm but also you need to keep values of the optimal
您需要为其XI的参与​​债券保持最佳口味的价值
you need to keep values of the optimal taste for its participant bonds of X I
taste for its participant bonds of X I you need this until you get to root this
您需要此，直到您扎根，这是由于
you need this until you get to root this is where this bullet changed because of
is where this bullet changed because of the work you will know what X is and
您将知道X是什么，然后您就可以标记和计算所有
the work you will know what X is and then you can mark and compute all the
then you can mark and compute all the other exit
其他出口
好的，您必须再次执行此操作，因为如果
then you can mark and compute all the other exit
all right again you have to do this because the if
好的，您必须再次执行此操作，因为如果
again you have to do this because the if you start selecting among them the sum
您开始选择其中最大的X J的总和
you start selecting among them the sum of the X J's that maximize this for
of the X J's that maximize this for whatever xre you're not going to get a
不管什么Xre，您基本上都不会获得一致的解决方案，所以您得到了
whatever xre you're not going to get a consistent solution basically so you get
consistent solution basically so you get the wrong solution and if I can show you
错误的解决方案，如果我可以向您展示这个问题，请抓住一些核心
the wrong solution and if I can show you this actually please to grab some core
this actually please to grab some core I'm going to come back to this right so
我要回到这个正确的位置
你知道如果你有一个马尔可夫链，你知道额外的可以说三个
this actually please to grab some core I'm going to come back to this right so
you know if you have a Markov chain and you know extra let's say can take three
你知道如果你有一个马尔可夫链，你知道额外的可以说三个
you know extra let's say can take three five or six you can take three values
五或六个，您可以取三个值，以此类推xn xn加1，所以这是一个
five or six you can take three values etcetera xn xn plus 1 so this is one
etcetera xn xn plus 1 so this is one possible this is another possible part
可能这是另一个可能的部分，对，这是最优值，然后
possible this is another possible part right this is the optimal value and then
right this is the optimal value and then basically from there you find what is
基本上从那里您会找到对应的先前值
basically from there you find what is the corresponding previous value for
the corresponding previous value for that value there is no and from there
该值不存在，并且从那里具有xn的对应值，并且
that value there is no and from there with the corresponding value of xn and
with the corresponding value of xn and then xn minus 1 so basically you will
然后xn减去1，所以基本上您会发现
then xn minus 1 so basically you will find which is the consisting the
find which is the consisting the consistent part that gives you
一致的零件，可以使关节最大化
consistent part that gives you maximization of the joint
再次，这是您需要编程的一些小事情之一
again this is one of this little things right that you need to have to program
right that you need to have to program the state in action alright and what is
运行中的状态还不错，这里有趣的是算法
the state in action alright and what is interesting here is again the algorithm
interesting here is again the algorithm gives you the impression to start with
给您以开始的印象，但是您只能通过以下方式将其最大化
gives you the impression to start with but you can only you can maximize it by
but you can only you can maximize it by a forward calculation but to figure out
前向计算，但要弄清楚参数，但要最大化
a forward calculation but to figure out the the argument the extras but maximize
the the argument the extras but maximize jointly the join you have to do the
联合，您还必须执行Marquart算法，这就是
jointly the join you have to do the Marquart algorithm as well and that's
Marquart algorithm as well and that's what this is all about let me see and
这是怎么回事，让我看看，我将从我们那里取下来
what this is all about let me see and I'm going to pick it up from where we
I'm going to pick it up from where we left it
离开它，所以基本上您会注意到
left it so basically you notice that from the
so basically you notice that from the previous comics let's say and I'm not
以前的漫画让我们说，我不确定您是否知道这可能会出现
previous comics let's say and I'm not sure you know maybe this will come in
sure you know maybe this will come in the next clock work but the clever
下一个时钟工作，但我们知道一个聪明的程序，多
the next clock work but the clever program that we you know the multi
program that we you know the multi rejection inspector you can okay working
拒绝检查器，您可以按照我们已经看到的方式处理邮件
rejection inspector you can okay working with messages the way we have seen
with messages the way we have seen before
前
显示通知，然后变成添加项，算法变得越来越多
with messages the way we have seen before
shows notifications then become additions and the algorithm becomes much
显示通知，然后变成添加项，算法变得越来越多
additions and the algorithm becomes much time and relation that this is working
如果您试图最大程度地利用
time and relation that this is working is basically if you try to maximize the
is basically if you try to maximize the joint of the effect with respect to X
关于X的效果的关节，您花了很长时间，这是相同的
joint of the effect with respect to X and you take the long this is the same
and you take the long this is the same as much rising with respect X the log of
相对于X上升X的P的对数
as much rising with respect X the log of P of X
P of X which most defining eggs to be able to
如果我定义H为
which most defining eggs to be able to the masses it's alright if I define H to
the masses it's alright if I define H to be the lots of the messages this is how
是很多消息，这就是算法的样子，所以
be the lots of the messages this is how the algorithm looks like okay so the
the algorithm looks like okay so the name of the message from JP y por el
目标是JP y节日信息的消息名称
name of the message from JP y por el festival values over time is the target
festival values over time is the target remember we have in the progress of the
记住，我们正在处理传入的消息，好吧，因为
remember we have in the progress of the incoming messages okay okay because with
incoming messages okay okay because with messages okay every a lot of these
好的消息，这些消息中的每一个都会非常小，
messages okay every a lot of these messages will be extremely small and
messages will be extremely small and basically this message will be an
基本上，此消息将是一个有用的信息，并且会得到很多零（10）
basically this message will be an informative and getting lots of zeros 10
informative and getting lots of zeros 10 to the minus 50 10 to the minus 30 etc
到负50 10到负30等遇到麻烦，所以这是另一个流程
to the minus 50 10 to the minus 30 etc get in trouble so this is another flow
get in trouble so this is another flow problem that in fact using logs right
实际上正确使用日志并意识到这两个任务的问题是
problem that in fact using logs right and doing these two missions aware is
and doing these two missions aware is the scope and even then there is the
范围，即使有高峰，如果您有，也可以找到Pataca lee
the scope and even then there is the peak that you can find Pataca lee if you
peak that you can find Pataca lee if you start even in math you have you known
即使在数学上也可以开始学习，您已经知道工具箱上的所有内容
start even in math you have you known the toolbox everywhere on
the toolbox everywhere on Jevon method muslim to ducks or any
Jevon方法穆斯林对鸭子或任何便士有一些问题，你是否发现
Jevon method muslim to ducks or any penny some problems you find whether
penny some problems you find whether they here's this message passing on what
他们在此传递的消息是，如果这种积极的使用感谢
they here's this message passing on what if the sort of positive use thanks for
if the sort of positive use thanks for the message this right but that
正确的消息，但这不应该是我的补充，我认为我
the message this right but that shouldn't be an addition i think well i
shouldn't be an addition i think well i wanted to show you because if you
想要向您展示，因为如果您编程时没有这个技巧，我会怎样
wanted to show you because if you program without this trick and i what i
program without this trick and i what i want to go you're not going to be able
想去，你将无法真正赚大钱，所以
want to go you're not going to be able to actually do large-scale profits so
to actually do large-scale profits so here's where the three kids so the
这是三个孩子的地方，所以信息是这是我们以前拥有的
here's where the three kids so the message is this is what we have before
message is this is what we have before I'm writing this in the context of the
我在消除期望a的背景下写这篇文章，所以你可以
I'm writing this in the context of the eliminating expected a so you can have
eliminating expected a so you can have the marks operator that's exactly the
标记运算符是完全一样的，所以我们不使用任何消息
the marks operator that's exactly the same thing so we use no messages all
same thing so we use no messages all right and so summation Alexei of this x
没错，所以这是x的总和阿列克谢，因为这是爱
right and so summation Alexei of this x naught and because this are love
naught and because this are love messages I can write this then you see
信息我可以写这个然后你会看到这将成为估计吧
messages I can write this then you see this would become estimation all right
this would become estimation all right and if I put outside because this term
如果我放学是因为这个学期的硕士课程，以及当我有一个
and if I put outside because this term of masters and when I have an
of masters and when I have an exponential inside okay we need this
内的指数函数好吧，我们需要看起来非常复杂的对，因为我们
exponential inside okay we need this looks extremely complex right because we
looks extremely complex right because we have to find the local summation and by
必须找到当地的总和，顺便说一句，所有估计都是非常典型的
have to find the local summation and by the way all estimation is very typical
the way all estimation is very typical in many other words in machine learning
换句话说，在机器学习中，好吧，你不能花那么长时间
in many other words in machine learning okay you cannot take this long and put
okay you cannot take this long and put it inside so novel destination in exit
它在如此新颖的目的地内，在任何幸存者的出口处都是两个指数项
it inside so novel destination in exit any survivors two terms as exponential
any survivors two terms as exponential of the law website this is what they
的法律网站，这就是他们所拥有的，因为我把指数
of the law website this is what they have and because I put the exponential
have and because I put the exponential of try so here I have a summation
尝试一下，所以在这里我有一个总结，这样您就可以接受所有这些，并且您
of try so here I have a summation alright so you take all of this and you
alright so you take all of this and you call it ln j alright this is where they
称它为ln j，这是卤化物a的指数，然后
call it ln j alright this is where they have exponential of halides a and then
have exponential of halides a and then you find out the maximum the prime
您发现最大的最大业务就是
you find out the maximum the prime business that maximizes that is the
business that maximizes that is the maximum basically from all the holidays
基本上所有假期都最多，所以你把它拉出来
maximum basically from all the holidays so you pull this out
so you pull this out and then with the leftist exponential of
然后用mij的左派指数-mi z好的，这就是
and then with the leftist exponential of mij - mi z okay and this is how
mij - mi z okay and this is how basically you have to implement the log
基本上，您在编写计算机时必须实现日志消息
basically you have to implement the log messages when you write your computer
messages when you write your computer program you can play with this and
程序，您可以与此玩，并说服自己
program you can play with this and convince yourself actually that this
convince yourself actually that this avoids other flow issues the way it did
这样可以避免其他流程问题，所以请研究此成员
avoids other flow issues the way it did here okay so study members of this
here okay so study members of this little algorithm Stephan actually if you
实际上，如果您在计算机程序中看到过小算法斯蒂芬（Stephan），
little algorithm Stephan actually if you see it in computer programs you know
see it in computer programs you know know that these nothing strange
知道这些没什么奇怪的东西基本上都是由代数来的，可以
know that these nothing strange basically comes by the algebra okay can
basically comes by the algebra okay can you do too much time algorithm graphs
你做太多的时间算法图当然有故事可以做
you do too much time algorithm graphs there are stories of course you can do
there are stories of course you can do anything you want to and if we use again
您想要的任何内容，如果我们再次使用某些消息，则该消息正常
anything you want to and if we use again some messages the message the normal
some messages the message the normal condition is basically the track system
条件基本上是在列表节点中保存消息的跟踪系统
condition is basically the track system that saved in the list node the message
that saved in the list node the message that we send to the clique the first
我们最后一次发送给集团的第一个因素是零团结
that we send to the clique the first factor is zero unity when we did last
factor is zero unity when we did last lecture this message will come after
讲座中此消息将在等于AB天然农药等于零之后出现
lecture this message will come after equal to AB natural pesticides is zero
equal to AB natural pesticides is zero and if the first value is a path then
如果第一个值是一条路径，那么该消息就是潜在肺部
and if the first value is a path then the message is the lung of the potential
the message is the lung of the potential of the factor and this is so this is the
的因素，这就是信息，基本上是
of the factor and this is so this is the message is basically that we were
message is basically that we were working on the last lecture if you want
如果您想将信息从要素发送到
working on the last lecture if you want to send a message from a factor to a
to send a message from a factor to a node potential if you take all the
如果您将所有消息从所有
node potential if you take all the messages to derive from all the
messages to derive from all the neighbors of the factor except at that
该因子的邻居（除了到达该因子的因子之外）与它们相乘
neighbors of the factor except at that arrived to the factor you multiply them
arrived to the factor you multiply them and then you have you basically
然后您基本上就消除了集成x12的麻烦，
and then you have you basically eliminate you integrate our x12 except
eliminate you integrate our x12 except all the nodes are involved in the fact
事实涉及的所有节点现在都可以接受，所以立即
all the nodes are involved in the fact will accept nowadays okay so instantly
will accept nowadays okay so instantly if you wanted to find the message and
如果您想查找消息，现在考虑因素
if you wanted to find the message and now since the factor
now since the factor is the message that central that no that
这是一个很重要的信息，那就是没有那一步当然是有害生物的因素
is the message that central that no that step of course the factor of pest so you
step of course the factor of pest so you might have been of incoming messages and
可能是收到的邮件，您与之抗争的因素是s，所以
might have been of incoming messages and you fought with them the factor of s so
you fought with them the factor of s so if you take those and exchange the
如果您拿走了这些，并将总和交换给match运算符，并且
if you take those and exchange the summations for the match operator and
summations for the match operator and you want to do a march time I will
您想进行一次游行，我会非常简单地联系图表的
you want to do a march time I will contact the graphs very trivial the
contact the graphs very trivial the message from dr. Novak's is the match
博士的话Novak是比赛清单，好的，我们要通知
message from dr. Novak's is the match list all right notice we're going to
list all right notice we're going to have a love of this and estimation here
当我做这个方程式时，很喜欢这个并在这里估算
have a love of this and estimation here so obviously when I make this equation
so obviously when I make this equation the implication is that now this mere
这意味着现在仅是实际消息的解决方案
the implication is that now this mere solutions of the actual messages right
solutions of the actual messages right there loves that's why you see here the
有爱，这就是为什么你在这里看到问题变成估计，然后又一次
there loves that's why you see here the problem became estimation and and again
problem became estimation and and again from a note the fact that you notice the
从注释中您发现产品开始振荡，其余的事实
from a note the fact that you notice the product becomes oscillation and the rest
product becomes oscillation and the rest is basic and the history when you reach
是基本的，当您到达根节点时，历史记录就可以找到
is basic and the history when you reach the root node you'll be able to find the
the root node you'll be able to find the value of x that does the maximization of
x的值，它使倍数最大化，其中所有
value of x that does the maximization of the fold where the summation of all the
the fold where the summation of all the messages coming from below and and then
消息来自下方，然后您需要回溯
messages coming from below and and then you need to do backtracking
you need to do backtracking from the root back all the way to the
从根一直回到列表，以找出x的含义
from the root back all the way to the list to figure out what of the x's that
最大化联合分配，因此，如果您有实施
maximize the Joint Distribution so then if you have an implementation of the
if you have an implementation of the sample of the target for photographs you
拍摄目标的样本，您可以将其转换为航海算法
sample of the target for photographs you can transform it to a nautical algorithm
can transform it to a nautical algorithm by changing the definitions of the
通过用匹配项更改鲑鱼交换术语的定义
by changing the definitions of the salmon exchanging terms with the match
salmon exchanging terms with the match operator and if you're not already doing
操作员，如果您尚未执行此操作，则必须在您的操作中执行此操作
operator and if you're not already doing this and you have to do this in your
this and you have to do this in your homework trying basically not to use
尝试基本不使用消息的作业现在将使用日志消息来查看
homework trying basically not to use messages will now use log message to see
messages will now use log message to see how things will look like
事情会是什么样子
这个奥秘与我们刚刚在简单的火车上讨论的一样
messages will now use log message to see how things will look like
this mystery is the same thing we just discussed from the on a simple train as
这个奥秘与我们刚刚在简单的火车上讨论的一样
discussed from the on a simple train as an example all right so that have a
好的示例，以便您可以在此块上看到一条消息
an example all right so that have a message that you see on this block I
message that you see on this block I think this is the negation of a graph we
认为这是我们之前的演讲中对图的否定，但现在
think this is the negation of a graph we had on an earlier lecture but now the
had on an earlier lecture but now the way I have it all the messages are
我拥有的方式所有消息基本上都是用于计算
way I have it all the messages are basically for the for calculating the
basically for the for calculating the maximum distribution and they are lost
最大分布，它们丢失了，因此它们是相同的，因此
maximum distribution and they are lost so from that they are the same so the
so from that they are the same so the message to this right is the same as the
右边的消息与从此粒子到此节点的消息相同
message to this right is the same as the message from this particle to this node
message from this particle to this node so whatever because this is same
所以无论是什么，因为这是相同的，无论从哪个消息接收不到
so whatever because this is same whatever message this not receive from
whatever message this not receive from this factor sense it called with an X
该因子的意义是使用X因子调用的，如果您要查找
this factor sense it called with an X Factor and if you want to find the
Factor and if you want to find the message let's see this is the message
消息，让我们看一下，这是因数n减去1 n而不是
message let's see this is the message from the factor n minus 1 n who is not
from the factor n minus 1 n who is not so this is we want to compute this
所以这就是我们想要在这里计算此消息，这就是我们想要的
so this is we want to compute this message here right this is what we want
message here right this is what we want to compute so this message you know what
计算，以便此消息您知道这次乘以传入消息的基础是什么
to compute so this message you know what the basis is this times incoming message
the basis is this times incoming message so what we're gonna do is we're gonna
所以我们要做的是相对于X n进行弧线匹配
so what we're gonna do is we're gonna take the arc match with respect to X n
take the arc match with respect to X n minus 1 Indianness HN minus 1 I'm
负1印度裔HN负1我正在承担我们现在拥有的潜力
minus 1 Indianness HN minus 1 I'm carrying the potential we now have the
carrying the potential we now have the real potential last incoming message
真正可能的最后传入消息在这里还可以，基本上是
real potential last incoming message which is here okay that's basically the
which is here okay that's basically the two relations that you need to be able
为此您需要能够传播消息的两个关系
two relations that you need to be able to propagate messages for this
你能告诉我你想保持什么功能吗
surrounding can you tell me what functional you wanna need to keep
what functional you wanna need to keep flaps here so here you compute the
在这里拍拍，所以在这里您可以计算出最大值，然后将其发送给
flaps here so here you compute the maximum of this and you send it to this
maximum of this and you send it to this message but we also need to keep tariffs
消息，但我们还需要将xn减1的关税保持为每个值
message but we also need to keep tariffs of xn minus 1 for what for every value
of xn minus 1 for what for every value of x and you should have figure out we
的x，您应该已经知道我们需要为我们的这个最大化
of x and you should have figure out we need to do this maximization for our
need to do this maximization for our past reviews of Excel so you are gonna
过去对Excel的评论，所以您将需要找到最佳xn减1作为
past reviews of Excel so you are gonna need to find the optimal xn minus 1 as a
need to find the optimal xn minus 1 as a function of xn and this to the sponsors
xn和this的功能给编写此文档的赞助商，然后我们就可以使用所有
function of xn and this to the sponsors who wrote this and then we can use all
who wrote this and then we can use all of this simple functions to go backwards
这些简单的函数可以向后退以获得上一节的所有内容，因此，当
of this simple functions to go backwards to get all the previous section so when
to get all the previous section so when I find it say here the maximum this
我发现这里说的是与您在此处看到的最大表达相同的表达
I find it say here the maximum this expression that you see here at the same
expression that you see here at the same time it gives me the optimal there the -
时间给了我最佳的-
好吧，我们不会接受所有显示下一个背部的权利，我们也需要
expression that you see here at the same time it gives me the optimal there the -
okay we will not accept all right showing the next back we also need to
好吧，我们不会接受所有显示下一个背部的权利，我们也需要
showing the next back we also need to keep collection as a function of xn plus
保持集合为xn加1的函数，而xn加1为xn加的函数
keep collection as a function of xn plus 1 and xn plus 1 is a function of xn plus
1 and xn plus 1 is a function of xn plus 2 until we say root note where we will
2直到我们说出根音，我们才能弄清楚他们将要做什么
2 until we say root note where we will be able to figure out what they would
be able to figure out what they would value is and then go backwards
值是，然后倒退
所以在此之前，如果我有时间告诉您有关作业操作树算法的信息，
be able to figure out what they would value is and then go backwards
so before and if I have time to tell you about the jobs action tree algorithm
所以在此之前，如果我有时间告诉您有关作业操作树算法的信息，
about the jobs action tree algorithm wanted to just put very few slides this
只想放几张这样的历史信念算法幻灯片
wanted to just put very few slides this sort of historical algorithm of belief
sort of historical algorithm of belief propagation on you know directed graphs
在您知道的有向图上传播没有循环，这些工作大部分是
propagation on you know directed graphs without loops these most of its work is
without loops these most of its work is in a little very important book VIPRE on
在一些非常重要的书中，关于概率推理智能的VIPRE
in a little very important book VIPRE on probabilistic reasoning intelligent
probabilistic reasoning intelligent systems you may even be able to find
系统甚至可以在网上找到这本书，因此，尺寸是
systems you may even be able to find this book online and so the dimension is
this book online and so the dimension is actually it somebody knows this is based
实际上有人知道这是基于消除该某些产品，所以这
actually it somebody knows this is based on elimination this some product so this
on elimination this some product so this comes out to be a sub J's
出来是sub J的，所以从某种意义上说，我会是
comes out to be a sub J's so in some sense I'm going to be
so in some sense I'm going to be evidently be different for directed
对于有向图，显然是不同的，但是您可以说
evidently be different for directed graphs but you can say that the
graphs but you can say that the algorithm actually looks the same okay
算法实际上看起来一样，所以这是有向图
algorithm actually looks the same okay so so this is this out directed graph
so so this is this out directed graph okay so we are looking at no text use of
好吧，所以我们正在寻找没有文字的孩子使用福林特效的方法
okay so we are looking at no text use of the forints effects wise of the children
the forints effects wise of the children affection etc and physically okay so
感情等，身体还好，所以这将是三个注意
affection etc and physically okay so this would be three note the the
this would be three note the the directionality of the edges basically
边缘的方向性基本上您今天就无法获得定向
directionality of the edges basically you get an undirected today with single
you get an undirected today with single path basically from one node to any
基本上从一个节点到任何其他节点的路径，尤其是能够
path basically from one node to any other node the especially to be able to
other node the especially to be able to understand this idea of belief
了解这种信念传播的想法，但是游戏是一样的
understand this idea of belief propagation but the game is the same
propagation but the game is the same algorithm so we are looking at X and so
算法，所以我们看X，所以想法是X的概率
algorithm so we are looking at X and so the idea is that the probability of X
the idea is that the probability of X this is sort of the marginal effects
这是一种边际效应，我们现在完成的方式提醒
this is sort of the marginal effects this way we have done up now reminds
this way we have done up now reminds information from upstream and doused
来自上游的信息和被淹没的信息，因此基本上结合了证据
information from upstream and doused so basically combines evidence
so basically combines evidence propagating from upstairs to and
从楼上传到楼下，从楼下传来证据
propagating from upstairs to and evidence propagating from downstairs
evidence propagating from downstairs okay and the idea that I can submit the
好的，我可以在上游和下游提交证据的想法
okay and the idea that I can submit the evidence when upstream and downstream
evidence when upstream and downstream has to do with the park the next
与公园有关，下一次失踪来自北部的证据
has to do with the park the next disappearance the evidence from upstate
disappearance the evidence from upstate from up and down you can see this right
如果我们在那里有证据，您可以从上下看到这项权利
from up and down you can see this right to go if we have evidence there and
to go if we have evidence there and evidence out there and you have to pass
证据在那里，你必须通过xxxx基本上阻止启动，所以
evidence out there and you have to pass through xxxx basically block start so
through xxxx basically block start so it's it does it separates the evidence
是的，它会将证据与上游和下游分开，所以如果您
it's it does it separates the evidence from upstream and downstream so if you
from upstream and downstream so if you want to compute the probability of x
想要给定证据计算x的概率，假设这是我们的
want to compute the probability of x given the evidence let's say this is our
given the evidence let's say this is our problem this is basically their belief
问题，这基本上是他们的信念，我们想计算一下
problem this is basically their belief all right that we want to compute about
all right that we want to compute about X so I can write this as the joint
X，所以我可以写成联合情感8除以面积
X so I can write this as the joint affection 8 divided by the area the
affection 8 divided by the area the probability of the evidence I because
证据I的概率，因为X耗散了证据，加上和
probability of the evidence I because the X dissipates the evidence plus and
the X dissipates the evidence plus and minus plus is the evidence of their -
减号是他们的证据-我可以写下的证据
minus plus is the evidence of their - the evidence down from it I can write
the evidence down from it I can write this yet + and against - and this is not
这还+和反对-这并不重要，所以我们不在乎，所以我
this yet + and against - and this is not important for it so we don't care so I
important for it so we don't care so I can write this as the probability of P X
可以写成PX减去给定X以及X加和的概率
can write this as the probability of P X minus given X and the X plus and the
minus given X and the X plus and the probability of x given Y X plus alright
给定YX加上正确的x的概率，因为X耗散了所有权利
probability of x given Y X plus alright and because X dissipates all right
and because X dissipates all right I can I don't need to keep the X plus
我可以不用在这里保留X加号，这样的信念可以写成
I can I don't need to keep the X plus here so this belief can be written as
here so this belief can be written as the community coming from upstream
来自上游证据的社区，这一次是
the community coming from upstream evidence and this time that is the
evidence and this time that is the probability coming from downstream
来自下游证据的概率确定，所以这基本上是在使用
probability coming from downstream evidence ok so this is basically using
evidence ok so this is basically using Bayes rule and the fact that we have a
贝叶斯规则以及我们在这里使用的耗散这一事实
Bayes rule and the fact that we have a dissipation here that I used in this
dissipation here that I used in this equation it allows me to write the
等式，它使我能够在其中写下您知道他们的信念
equation it allows me to write the the belief of the you know they in this
the belief of the you know they in this case is conditional on the evidence
本案以证据权为条件，但您可以想到
case is conditional on the evidence right but you can think of the
right but you can think of the calculations we were doing area for
我们正在计算边际的面积，它们是
calculations we were doing area for marginals that they were sort of the
marginals that they were sort of the Train so think of this as the Masters
培训，所以请考虑一下，因为来自上游五个学期的硕士课程来了
Train so think of this as the Masters coming from upstream five semesters come
coming from upstream five semesters come from downstream isn't it what we did
从下游开始，这不是我们计算边际权利时所做的
from downstream isn't it what we did when we computed the marginal right is
when we computed the marginal right is the product of the two messages but now
这两个消息的乘积，但是现在您注意到这件事基本上会
the product of the two messages but now you notice this things basically will
you notice this things basically will derive from Vegas rule
从维加斯规则得出，我不会依赖于
derive from Vegas rule I'm not going to level a depending by
I'm not going to level a depending by the simplistic we can philosophize on
我们可以对此进行哲学化的简单化处理，但您可以称其为“
the simplistic we can philosophize on this but you can call this you can put a
this but you can call this you can put a prior or next right and apply of naming
先前或下一个权利，并使用命名，这是折扣的可能性
prior or next right and apply of naming and this is the likelihood a discount
and this is the likelihood a discount from downstream but right now you know
从下游开始，但是现在您知道我们必须计算这十个
from downstream but right now you know we have to compute these ten that is
we have to compute these ten that is information coming from upstream and
来自上游的信息和来自下游的干扰
information coming from upstream and disturb that comes from from downstream
在组合上升中限制了下游信息，从而找到了x的概率
which in combined ups limit downstream information to find the probability of x
information to find the probability of x idea to that this message does we know
我们知道此消息可以通过本地消息传递来计算的想法
idea to that this message does we know can be computed by local message passing
can be computed by local message passing algorithm which we have seen okay and
我们已经知道可以使用的算法以及我们也拥有的最后一个想法
algorithm which we have seen okay and the last idea which also we have
the last idea which also we have discussed it they never sent to annul
讨论了他们从未发送过的通知，也没有将投资者发送给您的票据进行讨论
discussed it they never sent to annul and investors the note sent to you
and investors the note sent to you that's it so I am going to move you the
就是这样，我将向您移动方程式，我希望您实际
that's it so I am going to move you the equations and I want you to actually
equations and I want you to actually study them because they have a
研究它们，因为它们具有历史意义。
study them because they have a historical significance to be the
historical significance to be the conditional probability of x given the
给出证据的x的条件概率，我们将其作为
conditional probability of x given the evidence and we just take this as the
evidence and we just take this as the information coming now let me see what
现在收到的信息让我看看这里的定义是从哪里来的
information coming now let me see what the definition here coming from
the definition here coming from downstream so this comes this term
下游，所以这个术语lambda来自孩子，这是
downstream so this comes this term lambda comes from the children this is
lambda comes from the children this is what we derived various room and this is
我们派生出了各种各样的房间，这是来自父母的信息
what we derived various room and this is the information coming from the parents
the information coming from the parents okay certainly
好的，我要给你传递消息
okay certainly I'm gonna give you the message passing
I'm gonna give you the message passing algorithm but that's you what lambda is
算法，但这就是您的lambda和基于我们所拥有的PI
algorithm but that's you what lambda is and what PI is based on what we have
and what PI is based on what we have done alright so we need the information
好吧，所以我们需要来自孩子的信息，但要提取
done alright so we need the information coming from the children but extract
coming from the children but extract looking at this graph can return me with
看着这张图可以通过消息传递算法返回我，什么是
looking at this graph can return me with message passing algorithms what is the
message passing algorithms what is the information that comes from the children
从孩子到X的信息
information that comes from the children to X
再说一次，您在这张幻灯片上知道的木材，但请告诉我基本上哪些词
and again timbers you know there on this slide but tell me which words basically
slide but tell me which words basically I want to find all the information comes
我想找到所有来自精通2x的信息，我想成为这个
I want to find all the information comes from mastering 2x and I want to be this
from mastering 2x and I want to be this through messages of the children of X +
通过X + 2 X的子代的消息，这样圆形效果就是
through messages of the children of X + 2 X so that is round effect is the
2 X so that is round effect is the product at what
什么产品
是X发出欢呼的消息的协议，不是这种方式
2 X so that is round effect is the product at what
is the protocol for the messages the chinder of X send text isn't it the way
是X发出欢呼的消息的协议，不是这种方式
chinder of X send text isn't it the way we have done it before - with masters
我们之前做过-大师们都通过了，所以什么都没有
we have done it before - with masters passing all right so there's nothing
passing all right so there's nothing better one to fix is the program to
更好的解决方法是将程序添加到文件夹消息中
better one to fix is the program to folder messages which raised the
folder messages which raised the children of text right sent correct okay
正确的子项发送正确，好吧，现在我们计算一下
children of text right sent correct okay let's now calculate the information of
[掌声]
[Applause]
通过将遥远的上游和下游儿童的乘积发送到
the effects by taking the product of far upstream and downstream children sent to
upstream and downstream children sent to X to be able to do waste then I have to
X可以做废物然后我必须完成VEX的信息
X to be able to do waste then I have to complete the information of the VEX
complete the information of the VEX turns to children and also you are going
转向孩子，你也将不得不计算信息
turns to children and also you are going to have to compute the information
to have to compute the information access to its parents right you're not
访问其父母权利，您将无法计算这些
access to its parents right you're not gonna be able to calculate these
gonna be able to calculate these messages too long so you have to
消息太长，因此您也必须计算那些主节点
messages too long so you have to calculate those master as well
这在逻辑上特别重要，这是XS属于您的一部分的方法
this is what particular logically this is the method the XS it's part of your
is the method the XS it's part of your high so we have the question can it just
高，所以我们有一个问题可以吗，就是您了解有关问题的理论知识
high so we have the question can it just you know anomic look at the questions
you know anomic look at the questions look at this picture can you tell me
看看这张照片，你能告诉我在什么主甲板感觉上
look at this picture can you tell me what in what master deck sense to the
what in what master deck sense to the trade to you i what will it's time to
与您交易我该采取什么行动了-您是什么实际信息
trade to you i what will it's time to act - you are what information actual
act - you are what information actual center yard
中心院
和示例，如果我要问的程度是否与传递消息的故事有关
act - you are what information actual center yard
and examples right with message-passing story if I am asking whether extents to
和示例，如果我要问的程度是否与传递消息的故事有关
story if I am asking whether extents to you I so which is this message what
你我，这是什么消息，这是不会做的
you I so which is this message what wouldn't do
是，是从您的孩子那里收到的百分比，因为
yes percent is received from the from your children because the amount of
your children because the amount of facts here was the person after former
这里的事实是孩子们以前的消息之后的那个人好吧，因为你
facts here was the person after former messages from the kids okay because you
messages from the kids okay because you actually see from you are and you do etc
实际上是从您的视线中看到的，并且您进行了其他操作，因此，如果您需要再次执行此操作，
actually see from you are and you do etc so if you need to do this again the
so if you need to do this again the potential this is like the clip
就像剪辑可能会放松过去的生活一样
potential this is like the clip potentially relax live in its past times
potentially relax live in its past times the messages we received from all of the
我们从所有其他父母那里收到的消息，您注意到k不等于
the messages we received from all of the other parents you notice k not equal to
other parents you notice k not equal to I and then of course that you need to do
我，然后当然，您需要做的就是整合那个孩子，当然
I and then of course that you need to do is to integrate that child and of course
is to integrate that child and of course in this time we are going to have to
在这个时候，我们将不得不整合所有其他父母
in this time we are going to have to integrate all the other parents out
integrate all the other parents out right and what you got here semesters
正确，您在这里得到的学期与UI上的防御完全相同
right and what you got here semesters with this defense on a UI it's exactly
with this defense on a UI it's exactly the same as before shown with messages
与之前显示的消息相同，该波已被消息占据主导地位
the same as before shown with messages the wave have dominated with message
the wave have dominated with message passing it looks very plain but this is
通过它看起来很普通，但这是异常的，因为她是在
passing it looks very plain but this is an anomaly because she was developed in
an anomaly because she was developed in nineteen eighty fifty people talking
在任何认真学习中必须谈论的一百八十五人
nineteen eighty fifty people talking about must in learning in any serious
about must in learning in any serious extent right and so this has been
正确的范围，所以这在文本中是很常见的，所以您说他们
extent right and so this has been experienced in text so you say them to
experienced in text so you say them to children say so you're not a skiing not
孩子们说，所以您不等于说不是滑雪，但您也将所有
children say so you're not a skiing not equal to say but also you send all the
equal to say but also you send all the messages the parent effects and text
告知父效果和文本，这就是我们在此处拥有的所有
messages the parent effects and text which is what we have here with all the
which is what we have here with all the use integrate our
使用整合我们说，混乱之前的产品是
use integrate our she says the product before the mess is
she says the product before the mess is coming from all the kids but they shall
来自所有孩子，但他们实际上应与信息相乘
coming from all the kids but they shall actually to multiply with the message
actually to multiply with the message coming from that syndrome jail as well
也是从那个综合症监狱来的，分开就可以收到消息
coming from that syndrome jail as well and divide you can arrive the message
and divide you can arrive the message that you sent to a children's I as the
您以波旁阿拉伯语（Bourbon Arabic）的形式将其发送给儿童的I，
that you sent to a children's I as the Bourbon Arabic divided by the misses
Bourbon Arabic divided by the misses that the children James tends to you
詹姆斯的孩子们倾向于你，他们寄给你的信息是你吗
that the children James tends to you the message that they sent you do you
the message that they sent you do you remember when you like this right invoke
记住，当您喜欢这种权利时，请调用本次的消息，即孩子
remember when you like this right invoke this times the message that children
this times the message that children Jason's Plex which we're gonna listen to
Jason的Plex，我们要听我说，告诉您是否
Jason's Plex which we're gonna listen to what I'm gonna serve to tell you whether
what I'm gonna serve to tell you whether it's sent to us so we / it and you have
它已发送给我们，所以我们/您相信X的信念除以该消息
it's sent to us so we / it and you have this belief of X divided by this message
this belief of X divided by this message you know she has some electric
你知道她在那里有一些电优势，在某些情况下
you know she has some electric advantages fear there and in some of the
advantages fear there and in some of the implementations of this message passing
此消息传递算法的实现，您可能会看到这种类型的
implementations of this message passing algorithm you may see this type of
algorithm you may see this type of division so rather than saying do this
所以不是说今天K的乘法不一样
division so rather than saying do this multiplication for K different today
multiplication for K different today which another way of writing it right so
这是另一种正确的写法，所以军方/工资和
which another way of writing it right so the military / the message that wage and
the military / the message that wage and Jerry sent to X am I giving you a
杰里（Jerry）发送给X，是我让您有点头疼吗，是的，您
Jerry sent to X am I giving you a headache already a little bit yes you
headache already a little bit yes you said yes yes all right
说是是好的
幻灯片实际上已经放在网上了，我把它们放到今天就可以了，所以
headache already a little bit yes you said yes yes all right
the slides are up on the web actually which I put them to get today alright so
幻灯片实际上已经放在网上了，我把它们放到今天就可以了，所以
which I put them to get today alright so there they trade their pipe so you don't
他们在那里交易管道，所以您不必非要我写一个问题，
there they trade their pipe so you don't have to I'm just writing a questions and
have to I'm just writing a questions and tastes different than Jame and all of
口味不同于Jame，所有这些都无法复制，但是
tastes different than Jame and all of this can't duplicate this but yet it
this can't duplicate this but yet it takes so much of platform okay this is
需要这么多平台，好吧，这是给那些无所事事的教授的
takes so much of platform okay this is for professors who have nothing to do at
for professors who have nothing to do at night to just do lots of typing of our
晚上只需要对我们的幻灯片进行很多打字
night to just do lots of typing of our slides
slides okay ensue exception obviously this
好吧，这学期显然有他的幻灯片例外，但是在某些情况下
okay ensue exception obviously this semester with his slides and but in some
semester with his slides and but in some sense when I ask you to type the
当我要求您键入作业时的感觉是正确的
sense when I ask you to type the homework that is the reason right when
homework that is the reason right when you type things you look at them and you
您键入内容，然后看着它们，然后再看一遍，您说出了自己的意思。
you type things you look at them and you take a look again and again you say you
take a look again and again you say you know what doesn't look right and if it
知道什么看起来不对，如果看起来不对，那是不对的
know what doesn't look right and if it doesn't look like it is not right
doesn't look like it is not right and you can only say that when you type
而且您只能说，当您输入这些内容时，便会喜欢
and you can only say that when you type them when you do like that everything
them when you do like that everything but right good or bad you know I mean
但是无论好坏，您都知道我的意思，但是当您键入内容时，它在视觉上并没有
but right good or bad you know I mean but when you type it it visually doesn't
but when you type it it visually doesn't look right it's most probably not right
看起来不错，很可能是不对，好吧，任何问题都可以
look right it's most probably not right okay any questions all right
okay any questions all right so I am saying no because 132 so let me
所以我说不，因为132所以让我正确地做，我将要讨论
so I am saying no because 132 so let me do it correctly I am going to discuss
do it correctly I am going to discuss the junction tree algorithm and I'm
连接树算法，我要给你足够的时间
the junction tree algorithm and I'm gonna give you it's sufficient time
gonna give you it's sufficient time actually to go through this today is an
实际上今天要介绍的是介绍，我要给你
actually to go through this today is an introduction and I'm gonna give you
introduction and I'm gonna give you formally the structure of the algorithm
当我们在星期二回到它的朋友时，该算法的形式正式开始
formally the structure of the algorithm when we go back to it on Tuesday friends
when we go back to it on Tuesday friends by the way of the lecture today and also
通过今天的演讲以及星期二的演讲
by the way of the lecture today and also the lecture for Tuesday
the lecture for Tuesday one of the chapters of Michael Jordan's
迈克尔·乔丹（Michael Jordan）的书中的一章或“交界点3（Junction 3）”基本上是最好的
one of the chapters of Michael Jordan's book or Junction 3 is basically the best
book or Junction 3 is basically the best read for the subject okay
读这个主题还可以，虽然很基础但是有点地址
read for the subject okay very elementary but sort of addresses
very elementary but sort of addresses everything very nice
一切都很好
所以这是当然的，我将通过一个例子来做这件事，以激发
very elementary but sort of addresses everything very nice
so it's course again I'm going to do this through an example to motivate with
所以这是当然的，我将通过一个例子来做这件事，以激发
this through an example to motivate with the algorithm is so let's assume that we
该算法是这样的，让我们假设我们有一个有向图，看起来像
the algorithm is so let's assume that we have a directed graph that looks like
have a directed graph that looks like this
没关系，这显然不是一棵树
all right obviously this is not a tree right you can see it
正确，您可以看到它，我的意思是，如果它们不存在，
right you can see it I mean if it's they are was not there
I mean if it's they are was not there you can claim this two three but this is
您可以声称这两个三，但这不是一棵树，所以您知道我们必须看到
you can claim this two three but this is not a tree so you know we have to see
not a tree so you know we have to see how the this new algorithm is action 300
这个新算法如何动作300将帮助我们计算ryx
how the this new algorithm is action 300 will help us to calculate ryx all right
will help us to calculate ryx all right so what we're gonna need is I'm gonna
所以我们需要的是，我将带您完成整个流程，所以我
so what we're gonna need is I'm gonna take you through the process okay so I
take you through the process okay so I notice here so I'm going to convert this
注意这里，所以我将把它转换成无向图，正如我们所拥有的
notice here so I'm going to convert this to an undirected graph and as we have
to an undirected graph and as we have seen before the the first step is to
第一步之前看到的基本上是道德化，x5是平衡
seen before the the first step is to moralize basically and x5 is to balance
moralize basically and x5 is to balance so we wanna lies that we get an
所以我们想撒谎，我们得到一个无向图，看起来像那样
so we wanna lies that we get an undirected graph that looks like that
我们要说的是，我们要为此选择一个消除顺序
we are going to say we're going to select an elimination order of this
select an elimination order of this graph and we're going to keep that
图，我们将基本上保留消除板和
graph and we're going to keep that basically of the elimination plate and
basically of the elimination plate and we're going to pry interpretation we
我们将撬开解释，我们将消除点击通勤，因此
we're going to pry interpretation we commute elimination clicks so this
commute elimination clicks so this elimination cliques or the junction
消灭集团或基本上将要进入的第三个交界处
elimination cliques or the junction three that are going basically to
three that are going basically to contain the function the factors
包含功能与我们消除夹相关的因素
contain the function the factors affiliated with our elimination clips we
affiliated with our elimination clips we will see this on this particular example
在这个特定的例子中会看到这一点
所以这就是我们做对的事情
affiliated with our elimination clips we will see this on this particular example
so this is that what we got right
穆罕默德以某种方式出现在上一张幻灯片上，我将连接节点X 2
that somehow Muhammad is on the previous slide and I'm going to connect nodes X 2
slide and I'm going to connect nodes X 2 and X 3 this is what I am saying I'm
和X 3这就是我所说的，我要对它进行三角剖分
and X 3 this is what I am saying I'm calling it I'm going to triangulate the
calling it I'm going to triangulate the glass and can you just potentially why
玻璃杯，您能潜在地解释为什么我基本上需要预先点击吗？
glass and can you just potentially why basically I need to premonition clicks
basically I need to premonition clicks so somebody why do you need why do I
所以有人为什么你需要为什么我需要对图进行三角剖分
so somebody why do you need why do I need to triangulate the graph what
need to triangulate the graph what potentially benefit may exist there you
可能存在潜在的利益，您知道如果我一起打笔记的话，那是什么
potentially benefit may exist there you know if I call notes together what is
know if I call notes together what is the you know this is a big potential
您知道这是一个巨大的潜力，因为在那些毫无用处的人中，我们
the you know this is a big potential because in those for naught right so we
because in those for naught right so we need sort of to reduce that to 3 nodes
需要将其减少到3个节点，但要吹嘘的是
need sort of to reduce that to 3 nodes but blowing that there is a fundamental
but blowing that there is a fundamental property that I will show you one we
我将向您展示的财产我们将在没有任何照明的情况下完成这一工作
property that I will show you one we complete this that without any lighting
complete this that without any lighting in you're not going to be able to make
在你将无法使结点树算法左右，所以我们
in you're not going to be able to make the junction tree algorithm or so so we
the junction tree algorithm or so so we may need to tell you when we reach the
可能需要告诉您何时我们到达本示例的末尾，所以
may need to tell you when we reach the end of this example all right so the
end of this example all right so the first reason is we want to reduce the
第一个原因是我们想减少这个集团的规模，但是还有另一个
first reason is we want to reduce the size of this clique but there is another
size of this clique but there is another important aspect that we will see when
当算法产生OK时，我们将看到的重要方面是1 2 3 1 1 2
important aspect that we will see when the algorithm produces ok is 1 2 3 1 1 2
the algorithm produces ok is 1 2 3 1 1 2 3 ok now we're going to eliminate the
3好的，现在我们要消除链条，让我们看看下一个节点是什么
3 ok now we're going to eliminate the chain let's see what is the next node we
chain let's see what is the next node we want to eliminate now - ok that's our
现在要消除-好的，这是我们的订单，所以下一个消除集团是
want to eliminate now - ok that's our order so the next elimination clique is
order so the next elimination clique is 2 3 &amp; 4 2 3 or 4 this is what we left
2 3＆4 2 3或4这就是我们剩下的下一个淘汰集团是3 4＆5
2 3 &amp; 4 2 3 or 4 this is what we left the next elimination clique is 3 4 &amp; 5
the next elimination clique is 3 4 &amp; 5 so we will eliminate
所以我们接下来将消除三，三，四，五
so we will eliminate three so three four five the next
three so three four five the next elimination will be for North Shore
消除将是北岸，所以下周将下降五个
elimination will be for North Shore so the next week would be falling five
so the next week would be falling five and then I have time so the next week is
然后我有时间，所以下周就在这边，另外还有一个
and then I have time so the next week is now side and one in addition we kept
now side and one in addition we kept track of all these plygs and I'm going
跟踪所有这些plyg，我将摆脱存在的点击
track of all these plygs and I'm going to get rid of the clicks that there are
to get rid of the clicks that there are subsets of other maximal cliques all
其他最大派系的子集可以，所以您要保留什么
subsets of other maximal cliques all right so what are you going to keep
right so what are you going to keep parked at this much more clicks one two
停在更多的点击一二三二三四和三四有五
parked at this much more clicks one two three two three four and three four five
我将认为这是因为注释是在一位神中正确的，所以这是把戏
I am going to consider this as notes is in one God right so this is trick
in one God right so this is trick this is click one two three so the notes
这是单击一二三，因此请注意其中包含的变量
this is click one two three so the notes the variables that are contained in
the variables that are contained in notes you all are X 1 X 2 3 bottom of 63
请注意，你们所有人都是X 1 X 2 3，是63个出口排泄物的底部4 X 5，所以现在我要
notes you all are X 1 X 2 3 bottom of 63 export excretes 4 X 5 so now I'm going
export excretes 4 X 5 so now I'm going to do is I am going to pay attention to
要做的是我要注意您注意，我正在连接所有这些
to do is I am going to pay attention to you notice I am connecting all of this
you notice I am connecting all of this together but this is not really to me
在一起，但这对我来说不是真的，所以我们提出了三个
together but this is not really to me and so we come up with three that
and so we come up with three that involves this right and that click will
涉及这项权利，点击将随之而来，如下所示
involves this right and that click will come with it as follows look at this
come with it as follows look at this connection here how many nodes as the
在这里连接多少个节点作为剪辑步骤，你可以问多少个普通节点
connection here how many nodes as the clip steps you can ask how many common
clip steps you can ask how many common notes they have to come out this two
请注意，他们必须点击两次，谁是一个，所以我们要
notes they have to come out this two clicks who is one yes so we are going to
clicks who is one yes so we are going to design a three that has eight something
设计一个三点，有八点可以抵抗，重量是由
design a three that has eight something to resist and weight is accounted by how
to resist and weight is accounted by how many common notes served between these
这些最大派系之间有许多共同的注解，并且请您诚实地医治您
many common notes served between these maximal cliques and honestly doctor you
maximal cliques and honestly doctor you will believe it may will be C 1 C 2 C 3
会相信可能是C 1 C 2 C 3，
will believe it may will be C 1 C 2 C 3 and
因为这就是我们知道的
because this is what we okay you know
好的
all right
好吧，在这种情况下，显然这是
okay so in this case obviously this is
通常情况下，诊所和医院之间会发现一个实例的一致性
it's common to see one instance consistency between the clinics and in
consistency between the clinics and in the way we're going to be computing
如果X属于C 1和C 3，我们将要计算边际的方式
the way we're going to be computing marginals if X belongs to C 1 and C 3 it
marginals if X belongs to C 1 and C 3 it also has to belong to any other click
也必须属于通过此树从c1到c3的任何其他点击，所以基本上
also has to belong to any other click from c1 to c3 via this tree so basically
from c1 to c3 via this tree so basically we will not be able to propagate
我们将无法将消息从c1传播到c2到c3，因为
we will not be able to propagate messages from c1 to c2 to c3 because how
messages from c1 to c2 to c3 because how are you going to propagate messages
当这不是功能时，您是否要传播有关x3的消息
are you going to propagate messages about the x3 when this is not a function
about the x3 when this is not a function of X 3 so this property is called the
的X 3，所以此属性称为“运行交叉点”属性，所以如果
of X 3 so this property is called the running intersection property okay so if
running intersection property okay so if viable is common to
可行是常见的小费，但您会看到例如c1
viable is common to tip breaks but you see for example c1
tip breaks but you see for example c1 and c3 has to be also a fun intermediate
而且c3也必须是从c1到c3的有趣的中间单击，现在再说一次
and c3 has to be also a fun intermediate click from c1 to c3 okay now again I
click from c1 to c3 okay now again I mentioned that this is essential for
提到当您保持一致性时，这是必不可少的
mentioned that this is essential for maintaining consistency when you
maintaining consistency when you calculate multi notes on this graph I'm
在此图上计算多个注释，我将在其中进行实际讨论
calculate multi notes on this graph I'm going to actually discuss this in
going to actually discuss this in determined history right but right now
确定的历史记录，但现在基本上这是多长时间的动作3
determined history right but right now this is basically how long's action 3
this is basically how long's action 3 looks like it's not that you need it but
看起来这不是您需要它，而是人们对此的看法
looks like it's not that you need it but out of the way that people look at this
out of the way that people look at this algorithms in addition to these great
除了这些巨大潜力的算法外，
algorithms in addition to these great potentials the separators which are
potentials the separators which are basically the notes of their common
基本上是这些标记之间的共同点
basically the notes of their common between these marks
between these marks all right so the message passing from
好的，所以消息从
说c1是否要发送消息-狗屎-那将是
between these marks all right so the message passing from
say if c1 is going to send the messages - - that will be information that
说c1是否要发送消息-狗屎-那将是
- - that will be information that will update with variable only the
只会用不涉及先生的人来更新变量。帕累托一世
will update with variable only the person who is not involving mr. Pareto I
person who is not involving mr. Pareto I mean you know more and more in Steinmetz
意味着您在Steinmetz中对Schwann的了解越来越多，而事实并非如此
mean you know more and more in Steinmetz about that Schwann when this doesn't
about that Schwann when this doesn't depend on X was trying to try one side
取决于X试图尝试一侧到另一侧3基本上就像你有
depend on X was trying to try one side to side 3 is basically like if you have
to side 3 is basically like if you have this graph right you can make your own
这张图正确，您可以自己分配已发展的潜力
this graph right you can make your own assignment of potentials having evolved
assignment of potentials having evolved such 1x to explain if you have
这样的1x来解释您是否有涉及X 2 X 3的抗议者，
such 1x to explain if you have protesters of involve X 2 X 3 and
protesters of involve X 2 X 3 and similarly here it's great sports 5 you
同样，这是一项很棒的运动5如果您从
similarly here it's great sports 5 you have choices if you start from a
have choices if you start from a directed graph of how you do this
有向图，说明您如何进行此作业，但无论如何都要积极
directed graph of how you do this assignment but actively whatever
assignment but actively whatever optimization you have
您在这里进行的优化可以将其转换为台湾
optimization you have here you can transform this to Taiwan
here you can transform this to Taiwan Cyclops I predefined cupboard over this
我在此面具上预定义了“独眼巨人”，可用于旅行和历史记录
Cyclops I predefined cupboard over this mask on trips and history you can use
mask on trips and history you can use these misses passing away that we have
我们为牧师见过的这些未命中的小姐，现在您可以做到这一点
these misses passing away that we have seen for priests and now you can do this
seen for priests and now you can do this injunction treats even though the
即使原始问题与禁制令无关，禁制令仍然有效
injunction treats even though the original problem had nothing to do with
original problem had nothing to do with please so how do you do this you can
请这样您怎么做才能计算出这个clixsense的Masters
please so how do you do this you can compute the Masters this clixsense
compute the Masters this clixsense 2 from 1 to 2 and how do you compute is
2从1到2，您如何计算两个极值1的潜力，然后
2 from 1 to 2 and how do you compute is the potential of two extreme 1 and then
the potential of two extreme 1 and then what do you do you integrate X 1 out
您如何集成X 1呢？
what do you do you integrate X 1 out there is no incoming message from any
there is no incoming message from any part right so this is like the root node
部分正确，所以这就像根节点一样，没有传入消息，所以这是
part right so this is like the root node there is no incoming message so this is
there is no incoming message so this is n - 1 2 - let me see if there is another
n-1 2-让我们看看是否有另外一张图片
n - 1 2 - let me see if there is another picture if we look at the message from
picture if we look at the message from day 2 1 obviously I'm going to take this
第2天1显然，我将充分利用这种潜力，但是还有一个
day 2 1 obviously I'm going to take this potential all right but also there is an
potential all right but also there is an incoming message from city - -
从城市传入的消息-狗屎-那是然后您必须
incoming message from city - - which is that and then you have to
which is that and then you have to integrate variables that don't belong in
整合不属于有价值输出的分隔符​​的变量，因此
integrate variables that don't belong in the separator that's valuable export so
the separator that's valuable export so you integrate Explorer ok
您集成了Explorer，确定了，您如何计算，以便我可以完成
you integrate Explorer ok and how do you compute so I can finish
and how do you compute so I can finish when you finish if you're interested to
完成后，如果您有兴趣计算对应的边际
when you finish if you're interested to compute the marginals corresponding of
compute the marginals corresponding of the Barnabus X 1 X 2 X 3 corresponding
Barnabus X 1 X 2 X 3与此技巧相对应，但这是
the Barnabus X 1 X 2 X 3 corresponding to this trick but it is this is the
to this trick but it is this is the local potential sorry 1 times the
当地潜在的对不起1倍到达的消息
local potential sorry 1 times the message that arrives to see one from
message that arrives to see one from City the numbers and if you compute the
将数字放在城市中，如果计算X 2 X的边际，则导出将采用
City the numbers and if you compute the marginal of X 2 X the export takes the
marginal of X 2 X the export takes the local potential times the message one
本地电位乘以消息后，一种感觉就把消息传给了牧师
local potential times the message one sense the to take the message the priest
sense the to take the message the priest of the two and you're done actually it
这两个中的一个，实际上已经完成了
of the two and you're done actually it comes out to be exact
comes out to be exact if you are using it even when you have
如果您使用它，即使您有带有循环的图，并且已经
if you are using it even when you have graphs with loops and already we
graphs with loops and already we discussed the algorithm is called the
这里讨论的算法称为循环置信传播算法
discussed the algorithm is called the loopy belief propagation algorithm here
loopy belief propagation algorithm here looks you basically have two there is no
看起来你基本上有两个，没有这样的事情
looks you basically have two there is no such a thing as to the message from the
such a thing as to the message from the neighbors and then propagate them right
邻居，然后正确传播它们，因为您有循环，因此您需要
neighbors and then propagate them right because you have loop so what you need
because you have loop so what you need this initialize all this messages to
这会将所有这些消息初始化为也许或某物（如果有的话），以便谁
this initialize all this messages to maybe or something if any values so who
maybe or something if any values so who cares for sending messages to all the
关心将消息发送到所有其他节点，然后您可以应用
cares for sending messages to all the other nodes and then you can apply your
other nodes and then you can apply your classical Esther passing so if you have
经典的Esther过去了，所以如果您有环路，我会制作结点树
classical Esther passing so if you have the loops the junction tree I would make
the loops the junction tree I would make work and then lots of time works that if
工作，然后花费大量时间，如果您在那里设置文献，
work and then lots of time works that if you set the literature there some very
you set the literature there some very standard pain problems when it it pays
标准的疼痛问题，当它付出巨大的代价，并且不能正常工作时
standard pain problems when it it pays drastically and it doesn't work a lot
drastically and it doesn't work a lot okay but there's no proofs why it works
好的，但是没有任何证据说明为什么它在工作时会起作用，但实际上会起作用，
okay but there's no proofs why it works when it works but it actually works and
when it works but it actually works and it works for arbitrary graphs and you
它适用于任意图，您知道并且可以使其实际起作用
it works for arbitrary graphs and you know and you can make it actually work
know and you can make it actually work exactly okay so 146 the slides will have
完全可以，所以146张幻灯片上会有一个例子，这是我们所做的另一个示例
exactly okay so 146 the slides will have a thing that is another example we did
a thing that is another example we did in maybe giant Satyam the junction tree
在也许巨大的萨蒂扬（Satyam）中，结合树算法
in maybe giant Satyam the junction tree algorithm so when we come back on
algorithm so when we come back on Tuesday we can finish this general
星期二，我们可以从网上完成此通用推理算法
Tuesday we can finish this general inference algorithm is from online
inference algorithm is from online lecture so to make sure you have this
讲课，所以要确保你有这个转变，好吧，只保留两个
lecture so to make sure you have this transform you okay just reserve two
transform you okay just reserve two problems by tomorrow so you know what
明天有问题，所以你知道
等我通常在今晚最好的时间吃饭时，您可以停下来
transform you okay just reserve two problems by tomorrow so you know what
cetera you can stop by when I'm there usually eat up tonight's the best time
等我通常在今晚最好的时间吃饭时，您可以停下来
usually eat up tonight's the best time okay so
可以，然后呢